leoaffairs.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy

**_Introduction_**

This Privacy Policy is located at: [www.LEOAffairs.com](https://www.leoaffairs.com/) (this site), a site brought to you by Bright Mountain®, LLC.

Your privacy is very important to this site and Bright Mountain Media, Inc. (Bright Mountain®, us, we, or our as appropriate). Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. Please carefully read this Privacy Policy to gain an understanding of the treatment of your personal information as you make full use of all of the areas at this site.

Safe Harbor: The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed to the “Safe Harbor Principles” which provides a means for companies in the United States to satisfy the European Union requirement for “adequate” protection of personal information that is transferred from the EU to the United States. The “Safe Harbor Principles” are a set of data principles and frequently asked questions.

This Privacy Policy applies to any and all Personal Information that you provide to this site from the United States, the EU, or elsewhere.

Please be aware that other Third-Party Internet sites (such as promotional partners, advertisers, affiliates, etc.) accessible through this site may have their own privacy policy, data collection practices and policies, and Terms of Use. We are not responsible for the Third-Party’s actions, policies, or use of Personally Identifiable Information. Please check all of the applicable Policies and Terms of Use of the Third-Party(s) before providing Personally Identifiable Information through their linked site(s).

  1. **_Personally Identifiable Information that is collected:_**

Information may be collected in several ways at the different locations and/or pages of this site. Included in, but not limited to, this information is your street address, city, state/province, postal code, telephone number, and your website URL. Any information that you voluntarily supply would be used to assist you as you navigate this site.  Any information that you supply is voluntary on your part.

When you register at this site some personal information, such as your name and email address, are collected. You may be asked by the system for other information; any other information you provide is done so voluntarily. Included in, but not limited to, this other information is your full name, location, birthdate, occupation, and your website URL. The other information that you voluntarily supply would be used to assist you as you navigate the site. At other times we may ask you for personal information, including, but not limited to, when you upload videos, complete inquiry forms, post to any of the forums, or take advantage of other features at this site. The personal information is requested only when required to complete the intended transaction, and includes, and is not limited to, your location information, email address, telephone number, and your website URL.

When you Register at this site, you are asserting that you are 18 years of age or older, and you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy as well as the Terms of Use and all other related or like documents, including, but not limited to the Forum Rules, and Abuse and Violation.

You are no longer anonymous to this site once you have registered. After you register you will have a username and a password and the access afforded to registered users of this website.

Personal Information is collected from you by this site with the intention of providing to you (the user) a customized experience of this site, as well as to provide assistance to you as you navigate this site.

We do not collect or maintain your credit card information, all credit card or other financial information provided at the time of any purchase is gathered and maintained through a Third Party Merchant Account Provider. We do not maintain records of the information that you provide in any direct transactions between you and the Merchant Account Provider. This site only maintains information voluntarily posted into the _My Account_ area and/or inquiry forms, or any other non-financial information that you choose to post and/or submit to this site.

If you do not register or provide the personal information required to register, you will not be able to access those areas of this site, or use those features that require registration.

  2. **_An Explanation of Cookies and Their Use:_**

Cookies are small bits of text stored on your computer by the web browser that you use to visit websites on the Internet. These cookies are used to recognize you when you return to a website and will be used to enhance your visit to and experience at this site. In addition to recognizing you, any preferences that you have set will be remembered. Cookies may collect your domain name, and may be used to deliver targeted advertisements or content to you based on your online behavior or demographic information provided. If you set your browser to not accept cookies you may not be able to customize this site according to your preferences. If you access Third Party software and/or links available on this site, those Third Parties may collect cookies and/or Personally Identifiable Information from you.

  3. **_DoubleClick DART Cookie and Google Universal Analytics:_**

DoubleClick DART Cookie: Ads are served on this site through the use of cookies by Google as a third party vendor. The DART cookie is used by Google to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You can opt-out of Google Analytics used for Display Advertising and customize Display Network ads by visiting the Ad Settings in your Google Account. You may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by [**_CLICKING HERE_**](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) to visit the Google ad and content network

We have changed the Analytics tracking code on this site to support Display advertising. We have implemented the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting feature of Google’s Analytics based on Display. The data from Google’s interest-based advertising or Third Party audience data (including but not limited to age, gender, and interest) may be used with Google Analytics.

We will not facilitate a merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features based on the DoubleClick cookie without the user’s prior affirmative (i.e.: opt-in) consent to that merger.

Google Universal Analytics: These analytics tools are used by us to analyze the user interactions with our website. Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is not collected with these analytics tools.   [**_CLICK HERE_**](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881)  to access the Google Analytics Opt-Out page.

  4. **_Disclosure of Your Information:_**

Bright Mountain® may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. We may share information that you voluntarily provide to this site. When you voluntarily provide information you “Opt-In” which means that you agree to, or grant permission to, this site and its affiliates, partners, or Third Parties 1) sharing your personal information with our partners, affiliates, or Third Parties, 2) periodically sending you notices of special offers, advertisements, or other materials. The communications that you receive after you “Opt-In” will provide directions on how to unsubscribe or Opt-Out.

When required by law, or pursuant to legal proceedings we will disclose information, including but not limited to, in response to a court order or a subpoena, or law enforcement’s request.

Due to the very nature of some activities at this site your personal information will be revealed to other users of this site.

We may provide access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

If we are acquired by or merged with another company, we may transfer information about you. In any event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  5. **_ Accuracy, Security, Storage of User Information, and Policy Changes and Questions:_**

You may edit, change, or correct your information to assure the accuracy of your personal information provided to us by logging into this site using your current user name and password to access your _My Profile_ area. You also can change and/or update your settings by logging into this site using your current user name and password to access your _Settings_ area.

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy, the accuracy of your personal information, or how the collected information is used can be submitted by [**_CLICKING HERE_**](https://www.leoaffairs.com/contact-us/).

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date of posting to this Website. This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time; please revisit this page periodically to read the latest Privacy Policy. A link to this Privacy Policy is maintained on _this site_. If you decide to preclude your information from any new and/or different use as disclosed in a revised Privacy Policy, please contact us by [**_CLICKING HERE_**](https://www.leoaffairs.com/contact-us/), or visit the following website to submit an unsubscribe request:[ www.LEOAffairs.com](https://www.leoaffairs.com/contact-us/).

We use a secure server to house any user information that we maintain, and employ reasonable security procedures in the protection of the security and integrity of the information. However, due to the nature and the environment of electronic communication and the Internet we cannot make assurances to you regarding the safeguards that we have put into place preventing unauthorized access to, maintain security of, or correct use the data or the information collected. Bear in mind that no data transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while our intention is to protect your personal information, this site cannot and does not guarantee, warrant, or ensure the security of any information that you transmit to or from us online, post on this or any related sites, or provide in registering or making purchases at this site. You transmit any information or data at your own risk.

**Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)**

Bright Mountain Media works with merchants and users around the world, including in the EEA. If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend, delete, port to another service provider, or object to certain uses of your personal data. If you are a merchant, a partner, a visitor, a customer of Bright Mountain Media’s websites, please reach out to us using this email privacy@brightmountainmedia.com. Additionally, if you are located in the EEA, we are generally processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have to pursue the following legitimate interests, either for ourselves, our merchants, our partners, or other third parties:  
To provide merchants and others with our services;  
To prevent risk and fraud on our websites;  
To provide communications, marketing, and advertising;  
To provide reporting and analytics;  
To provide troubleshooting, support services, or to answer questions;  
To improve our services and websites.  
When we process personal information to pursue these legitimate interests, we do so where we believe the nature of the processing, the information being processed, and the technical and organizational measures employed to protect that information can help mitigate the risks to the data subject.

  6. **_Opting-Out:_**

To stop receiving e-mail from us: follow the instructions supplied at the bottom of each e-mail, or at the website: [www.LEOAffairs.com](https://www.leoaffairs.com/contact-us/).

To stop receiving e-mail from any partner, affiliate, or Third Party please contact that partner, affiliate, or Third Party as instructed in their Privacy Policy.

  7. **_Children’s Privacy_**

This site is intended to be a general audience website and is not intended for use by children (those who are 16 years of age and under). Consistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, this site does not knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. Those 18 years of age and under should not provide any personally identifiable information through this site. This site is not responsible for, or in any way liable for, any results of use of this site if an individual makes a false declaration of their age.

  8. **_Use of this Website:_**

The Terms of Use Agreement of this site governs your use of this website. To see the full Terms of Use Agreement please go to [www.LEOAffairs.com](https://www.leoaffairs.com/message-boards/terms-of-use/).

  9. **_Advertising:_**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ ** _CLICK HERE_**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) ** _._**

  10. **_Use of this site:_**

This site is for non-commercial use. You are not permitted to use this website or its contents for any commercial or non-personal purpose (direct or indirect). We reserve the right to prevent and/or terminate the access to this site of any party that violates in any way this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use, or any other policies and related documents pertaining to this site.
